???
This is an announcement.
Due to budget cuts, this episode will be
using puppets instead of being animated.
Hey, Pencil! How's it going?
Oh, nothing. Just looking at clouds.
Watching clouds, huh? You seem pretty bored.
Let's go do something fun, like jumping off a cliff!
Pencil! I didn't mean it literally!
WEE-oh, you didn't mean it literally?
No.
So, we're not cliff jumping?
Oooweh!
Let's watch clouds with Pen!
Yeah!
Oooaaah!
Why, in fact, I am!
Doing what?
Ohhh, you knooow!
Oh, cool! I want one!
Weuuueuuugh!
AWESOME!
I want one, too!
Yay! I have one, too!
AHHHHH!
AEEEEEEHHHH!
AEEUUGHUHAEUXXHEAUHEAUHHH!
Ha-ha-ha! These losers look like they're
having so much fun with their dolls!
Yeah!
Ah, phew!
Rah!
Phew!
Reueuuuuughhhh heeuuuugh!
Yuh!
I've been rescued!
YAAAAAY!
HEEUUUGHHHBUOOHUHBHHCHHSH!
BLAAAHAAKEBUSHAAAA!
AAAAAAAAA!
SPONGY:
Hi.
Spongy, what happened to you?
Wha?
It's great to be puppets!
Yay! This is awesome! Ha-ha-ha!
This is the best thing ever! Yay! Woo-hoo!
Yay! Hoo-ray! Hoo-rah! Waa-yaa-yaa!
Yaaaay! Yaaa-haaaay! A-ha, yay!
APRIL FOOLS!
You were fooled, weren't you? Ha, ha.
Ha-ha! Even I was fooled!
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
Last episode, Rocky's barfing habits,
Bubble's love for ice cream, and Pen's cheating
caused them to fall into the danger zone.
Now, it's time to see which of
the three of you will be eliminated.
♪ OMG! There's points now ♪
♪ Who'll go home? We'll just see... ♪
♪ It's Cake at Staaake! ♪
So, this time, we have a blueberry pie.
Yoy-mm!
But be gentle, because it's explosive.
Uh-explosive!?
So if you get some pie, you are safe.
If you don't, you will be eliminated.
Anyway, we got 259 votes.
That's not very many!
No, it's not.
Regardless, we have another
large crowd watching this event today.
I like to keep things private. Moving on...
Since Pencil, Spongy, Firey, Blocky,
Tennis Ball, Leafy, and Ice Cube
were not in the danger zone,
they are safe.
There are only two slices left.
Bubble...
you only got twenty-three votes, so you are safe.
Yoya!
Now it's down to Pen and Rocky.
Let's show the votes.
[DRUM ROLL]
[CRASH!]
That means Rocky is safe...
...and Pen will be eliminated.
Now that Pen is gone,
you are the final nine contestants.
YAY!
Isn't that wonderful?
Yes! That IS wonderful!
So anyway, these are your current scores.
So, who's going to be up for elimination?
Shush. I'll get to that later.
The sixteenth contest is a bowling contest.
Yay!
Since armless people cannot
bowl, they are disqualified.
Aww!
So, let's get down to business.
We will go in alphabetical order, so Blocky is first.
Okay! Hyup!
You only get one shot, so Bubble is next.
Whoaaa!
Ha-ha!
Hyeh!
Yeah, let's do this!
WHAAATEEEVAAA!
Pencil is last. Go.
Yeah!
So that's it.
Yay! So do I get points for the pins I knock down?
Nope. This time, you get to take away points.
For every pin you knock down, you can subtract
thirty points from any other contestant's score.
[GASP!]
So, let's begin.
Leafy, you knocked down three pins.
You can subtract ninety points.
What is your decision?
Hmm...
I think it's pretty obvious what I want: EQUALITY!
Ten points off everyone.
Pencil, with five pins,
you can subtract 150 points.
What do you want?
Same as Leafy, but I gotta stick with my alliance.
So that means twenty-five
points off everyone else.
Blocky, your seven pins mean
you can subtract 210 points.
Okay, let's see...
Let's drain away all of Bubble's points.
Oh, no-io-ho!
You have 112 points left to subtract.
Great! I'll take away fifty-six points
from Leafy and Pencil each
for even thinking about lowering my score!
Grr!
Finally, Firey. You can subtract 300 points.
Ooh, that's a lot.
Well, Ice Cube's like my opposite,
so she should lose 100 points or so.
Spongy's too far ahead of everyone else now.
Let's take 100 points off him as well.
Blocky was really mean to Bubble.
He should lose forty points.
You have sixty points left to subtract.
That's perfect! I'll take thirty points off
Leafy and Pencil for subtracting my score!
And that's it. These are your current scores.
Okay, you've caused enough craziness.
Can you finally tell me who's up for elimination?
Actually, all of you are up for elimination.
What? Huh? What?
Except for Firey, because he
knocked down all ten pins.
He has immunity.
- Yay!
- Grr!
Oh, green with envy, aren't you?
That's the unique twist to this episode.
So, voters. Everyone. Yes, you.
Choose who you think should
leave the Battle for Dream Island.
Cast your vote by typing it
in the comments section BELOW.
Voting ends April 10th.
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
ANNOUNCER:
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Wuehehweh, ooueheh-WEH!
Isn't that a wonderful noise?
Well, now you can listen to that noise 24/7
thanks to our revolutionary headphones!
Listen to it while you walk.
Listen to it while you sleep!
These headphones can only play that noise-
and why would you ever want
to listen to anything else?
They also have a volume up button.
No volume down button.
Wough.
And best of all,
our superglue makes them unremovable!
So yeah, buy now!
???
Next time, on BFDI...
We will be throwing frisbees.
Ooh, yay!
Eh!
And one recommended character will join the game.
[GASP!]